Alright, I want to start by laying out some of the goals of the course.
So, number one is to understand design and implementation of operating systems.
Yeah, design is sort of high level structure and implementation is really about what the code looks like,
and we'll be spend a lot of time with both.
And in the interest of getting deep understanding of what's going on,
you'll get hands on experience with a small, with a small operating system, the xv6 operating system.
And in addition to actually looking at an existing operating system,
that you'll be in the labs get a bunch of experience,
extending the operating system, modifying, improving its behavior
and writing system software that it uses the operating system interfaces, [] application.